I am Saho Tanaka from Clan Pop.
I am Hanon, playing the role of Kyushu Girl.
Pleased to meet you.
This is the second half of the show.
I would like to continue our conversation from the first part,
The first half was quite private.
It was like a "baritone".
I was talking about not making it cute,
There were also some idol-like characters.
I heard that from April there will be five female actors in the group.
I heard that the five-member group has changed things,
I was wondering if there were any differences from the 4-member group.
When I saw your performance,
The balance of the five members is very beautiful,
There is a height difference between us,
The new member is about the same height as me,
The balance of the five of us is much better,
I would say there is a sense of cohesion, which I felt when I watched the performance.
When there are four members in the center, it is not so common,
When there are five members, there are two in the center, so it is quite common.
It looks beautiful.
It is only possible with five people. That's true.
We are a group of five as well,
When we split in half, we become 2 or 3,
It's like, "Isn't this one better than this one? It's like that.
Yes, that's true. That's true.
When we go out to eat, there are often seats for four people,
In Gyoshin, there was a manager in front of us,
And then there are four members in the four-seater section.
So it's the manager and one other person.
But they were very close, so it was almost the same,
It was also difficult to divide the seats.
When you ride a roller coaster, for example,
It is true that when you ride a roller coaster, there is one person left over, isn't there?
It is difficult.
There are four waitstaff at amusement parks, too,
That's right. Yes, there are.
It's like that with coffee cups.
It's more convenient to have an army,
Wait, wait, wait. There are times when the number of troops is better.
Yes, there are.
Yes, there are. Performance, for example.
Yes, there is.
It's pretty tight,
I wonder. I don't know.
The five of us have been together for too long.
Have you been here long?
How long?
But it's been the five of us for about three years.
No, no, no, no.
Do you have a secret?
Uhhh...
I don't know.
Eh~...
We've been together too long.
That's right.
Until now, there were six of us on board.
Including that time, we have been together for about 5 or 6 years.
I don't know anymore.
It's nice. But it's good.
Thank you very much.
No, no, no.
Thank you for watching.
I wonder. But,
I had the opportunity to go to Fukuoka a couple of times,
I have been to Fukuoka a couple of times, and I have been to live shows in Taiwan,
I had the impression that there were many good-looking idols in general,
They are beautiful and have cute faces,
I have an image that there are many good-looking idols who are beautiful and have cute faces, but also move and perform in a flashy way,
What do you think?
What do you think? I don't know.
But there are many groups whose performances are at a very high level.
Yes, there are. Quite a lot.
On the other hand, we are from Tokyo,
What kind of image do you have of idols?
I have an image that there are a lot of redheads.
Is that true?
I've been to live shows in Taiwan and seen idols all over the place,
Thin! They are so cute! I think they are cute!Thin! Cute! Like that.
Sometimes we look like potatoes.
That's not true.
It's more like we are advertised, or we have a great image.
I still feel like this when I walk around Shinjuku or Shibuya in Tokyo,
Even I look like this. Shinjuku, for example.
I don't know where the exit is.
I don't know how to get out.
Even when I get to the concert venue, I'm a little confused,
I don't know which exit to take.
There are places where you don't know which exit to take.
The audience in Fukuoka also looks at live performances differently from those in Tokyo.
I see.
In Fukuoka, people tend to watch carefully,
Tokyo audiences enjoy the show by copying the choreography together.
There is a difference between Fukuoka and Tokyo in the way we enjoy music together.
I see.
I haven't been able to visit Fukuoka much recently,
When you go back, I will show you around,
I will show you around.
Really? Yay!
There are so many delicious foods there.
Please do.
I'm looking forward to it.
Q. What is your favorite recent makeup?
I wonder.
I thought your skin was so smooth,
Do you have a skin care routine?
I'm always on the lookout for new products, but I can't buy them when I think they're good.
That's right.
If I use a different one, I have the feeling that I'll end up with something else,
I always have something to help me out.
May I ask what kind of things you use?
There is a pack that I heard that will definitely cure the disease,
That's right.
Something like that.
Like a magic dream.
There was something like that,
If something goes wrong and I'm in a bad situation, I just need this.
I'll ask you to teach me later.
Yes, by all means. By all means.
I see. I don't know much about it at all,
What? It's slippery.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's very smooth.
Is it because of the makeup artist?
Thank you for everything.
I see.
It's cute.
Let's go that way.
Pre-live routine.
Like a routine before a live show.
Do you have a routine that you have to follow before going to a live show?
I wonder. I don't think I am the most particular about it,
I wonder.
It really depends on each time.
If I'm hungry, I'll eat,
If I'm not sure about the script, I'll eat.
I wonder.
But I do jump right before I go out for a live performance.
Jumping?
I mean, with my body.
Like a 10-second jump.
Ten-second jump?
I once saw you do it in a TV drama,
After I saw it, I thought that I had seen something like that before,
It seemed to get me fired up a little bit,
I'm sure. It makes me feel lighter.
I sometimes fly during SEs. Sometimes.
I can tell. I'm running all the time.
Really?
I think so.
You want to be physically active.
Yes, I do.
That's true. Maybe I'll go for a run too.
Let's run.
You seem to be able to move, don't you? Even in a live performance.
For that.
For sure. That's for sure.
Are there some members who are very particular about what they do?
But there are not many who are that particular.But there are not many kids who are that particular about it.
Like, they really don't eat before a concert,
I get a stomachache, so I don't eat much. That's about it.
Is that about the extent of it?
Yes, I guess so.
I'm very concerned about it.
Really?
I wonder what he is doing.
I'll ask him.
I don't know much.
So, we will be performing at Tokyo YakanLand vol. 2 on June 6,
I didn't perform at the last Tokyo YakanLand, and this will be my first time to perform at the second one,
I would like to get some advice from you.
I don't know. I don't know, but you are very close to the audience.
It's a very homey atmosphere,
It's fun, so I hope people can enjoy the show without being overawed.
And the play?
Yes, we did. Yes, I did.
That's what makes me the most nervous.
Because I don't skip lines.
I don't skip lines,
I had acted with other people before.
So I'm just going to enjoy myself.
What role did you play?
I played a receptionist at a call center, and I played the part of a receptionist who takes calls,
But it was surprisingly good,
I was taking calls.
I've never done that before. I've never actually done it.
But you do make phone calls, don't you? Usually.
Just like that.
I'm looking forward to it.
What kind of role would you like to play?
I played a cab driver the other day.
Yes, yes, yes.
You had a role, didn't you?
As a customer,
A bit of a strange character.
You want to play a funny character?
I'd like to play a strange character, a funny character.
I'll ask you to do it.
I don't know. That was really weird.
If I say it now, I can do anything.
I'll be fine.
There are other performers in the show.
Is there anyone you are interested in or have a connection with?
I was on the Gigtakahasutu tour with them before,
Metruna and I used to tour together on the Gigtakahas tour,
Also, I'd like to share with you a post by Yuka Yasumori of Iginari and Hokusan.
I was going around with them, so I was a little bit close to them,
We were going around together, so I felt a little bit closer to her,
I had a sense of kinship with her,
I hope to take this opportunity and others to get to know you better.
So, more, then.
It's just a trial.
Let's work together.
Let's do our best.
I also have a lot of friends like Hana Kojima, who was with me last time in Vol. 1, and Yuri Koi, who was with me last time,
I was with Hana Kojima and Yuri Koi last time,
Harumahana had done a tour with Crown Pop and Haruma before,
That kind of thing,
Sounds like fun.
I think they seem to be having a good time together,
I think we have something in common.
I wonder if they have something in common.
I'm also a member of the staff, so to some extent I do have something in common with them,
I will do my best to blend in.
Please come in.
I'm glad to have you here.
If you are open to us.
Not at all. Everyone is so kind,
We'll be happy to have you.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder what it will be like.
While keeping the goodness of Vol. 1,
2, I hope we can make it more up to par so that people can enjoy it.
I hope you all look forward to it.
That's all. That's all for now,
How was it?
But by having this conversation with you before the night land,
I am looking forward to getting to know you all better in the future,I also have an increased desire to get to know everyone better in the future,
I am happy to get to know Sahorn better, and I want to get to know him better,
I am happy that Sahorn and I are getting to know each other better, and I want to get to know him better.
Thank you very much.
I also wanted to talk to him before the night land,
I was very happy to have this opportunity.
Let's get to know each other better.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now, this is Saho Tanaka of Crown Pop and Kanon who played the role of Kyushu girl,
I am Saho Tanaka from Crown Pop and Kanon from Kyushu Girls.
Thank you very much.
See you soon.